Hey everyone, welcome to today's video focusing on heels and tights and integrated heels into tights
because do you remember a few weeks ago when I tried on the blue latex catsuit with the
integrated heels? It looked so good on the pictures but it was so hard to get into and I struggled so
much so I went on a search, a quest to find something similar but easier to get into and I
found these heels integrated into the heights which I'm going to show you today which will
be my main focus point of the video but I have also some other heels and heights but
yeah oh I think this is going to be really interesting so let's start by the way everything
I'm showing you today is from the online shopping platform Temu. Thanks for partnering up with me
for this video. So we have one panel of fabric going from the shoe straight into the heel so no
seam is just sewn onto the shoe itself here but it's just one long panel of fabric.
and we have pointed heels what I also think is really cool is that the heel itself is
coated in the fabric of the shoe so it's one really seamless cool look
Let's put them on and I hope it's going to be really quick because that's what I was
looking for.
Wow, that was easy.
You just have to get into the shoe with your toes.
That's so smooth I can't even grab the fabric to pull it up again.
Quick tip if you're struggling to move your tights up your legs because they're so smooth.
your fingers a bit with some water and then use the wet fingers to pull
everything up. Don't worry the water drops will disappear and they're going
to dry on the fabric. That way you can get a better grip on the fabric. The
fabric itself is really smooth so it's super comfortable and it's really shiny
slightly see-through as you can obviously see here because you can see my panty.
And I'm wearing heels in the size 40. I ordered 40 and they fit really good so
they're true to size and I have enough space for my toes which is not always
the point in pointy heels so I'm happy about that.
and I think this look is so cool with integrated heels and tights it's just
like really one I know in Germany I say one guss aus einem guss no idea what that
means in English next I want to show you two looks with the tights to put really
some kind of spotlight on them and highlight them with outfits I have dress
and a bodysuit and I think I'm going to start with the bodysuit.
I think that's a really cool look paired together with a PVC bodysuit.
Everything is shiny but the red and black combination is really wow and really
bright so that's definitely an eye catcher the heel side thigh heel tights heel tights heel
heel tights what's this called it doesn't have a really proper name does it I don't know
just thinking of occasions to wear this but to be honest i don't know you could put like
red horns on top of your head and then go as a devil for halloween or carnival because um
yeah i think these are the main focus point of the outfit i think they make the leg look really
nice and like an optical illusion with the heel that flows into the leg so it's
really a really nice look I think I have to get them other colors as well like
black or maybe dark blue that could be really cool and now for a second look
I'm going to change into this dress I just learned the tricky part about these
heel tights is not getting into them but getting into other stuff afterwards
because with the body and also with the dress you have to somehow put the heel
and pointy shoe into the garment and slide through it to get dressed. It's
better to have help for that so you don't rip anything. But this is the
second look and I think it's a really really elegant look. Like I could go on
red carpet with this. I think it's really something extravagant. Totally like the
combination I have to say. And again I'm realizing I do not have red accessories.
I think it's finally time to start looking for something red because from
time to time I do have red clothes or items which I need to spice up a bit.
like for example a cute red handbag would be really nice now. I also got a few other items
from Timu. Some tights and some black basic heels which I won't show you next because it's always
good to have something like this in your closet. You know I always joke around that I am the
destroyer of tights because I ruin them a lot and I rip a lot of them and tear them apart and
Normally I wear them one, two, three times before I make a hole in them.
So it's always good to have some budget tights in your closet and I think Timo is a great platform to go shop them.
The same thing about the basic budget tights can be said about shoes.
So I got a pair of plain black shoes to match like basically every dress or every outfit
putting me on.
with the tights by the way a houndstooth pattern and the basic elegant black heels I
upgraded this dress from me to like that's really cool great outfit because I think
they complete the look and as I said I just love these kind of shoes that you
can wear to everything get into really easy and which are great basic
second time I want to show you just have to unpack it always nice we have a neat
little bag to store them in after again
Tight Swiss stripes.
Let's change.
second look tights look and you know what this reminds me of contouring like if you want to
contour your legs dark parts on the sides and the bright part in the middle so they look um slimmer
I don't know if that works but I just had the impression of that but it also looks funny with
the with the stripes from behind or the side I think it's a really fun pattern
and again I think it looks really cool together with a dress and shoes I think even better than
the first tights so this would be my preferred look have a look at the Temu store of course I
link everything down in the description text if an item is not available anymore look around in
the shop they have a lot of similar stuff so I'm sure you will find something you like
I think for tights on a budget these work really well and you have a whole variety of patterns to
choose from especially good if you like need a special pattern for a model party or for
a really special occasion and you're looking for stars or dots or whatever I mean for me as well
I do a lot of photo shoots I do a lot of video shoots I do need a lot of tights with different
pattern so it doesn't get boring which I also like to do I love tights I have
like a bunch of them all right I hope you had fun today I certainly did and I
have to check out the pictures with the red tights because I think on pictures
they're really cool as well anyway leave a comment hit the like and subscribe
button and check out Teemu thanks for watching see you around next time bye